舜天信兴样衣管理系统从客户会议开始：客户提出欧洲市场、轻户外、浅色系，并给出参考图。业务员直接打开业务前台找可借可推的款。
The Suntien Xinxing Sample Management System starts from a client meeting: the buyer asks for European-market, light outdoor, pale-color styles and provides a reference image.
业务员用姓名、业务组和手机号登录。后续收藏、已选、PPT、借样申请和费用账单都会归到个人和业务组。
The salesperson signs in with name, team, and phone number. Favorites, selections, PPT records, loan requests, and bills are tied to that person and team.
业务员按客户需求筛选设计样衣和大货样品，查看在库、季节、品类和颜色，让客户快速看到可推款。
Sales filters design and bulk samples by availability, season, category, and color so the client quickly sees pitch-ready styles.
客户给参考图时，业务员点击相机上传图片，系统在可见样衣里找相似款并按匹配度排序。
When the client gives a reference, sales clicks the camera, uploads the image, and the system ranks similar visible samples.
点爱心代表收藏客户感兴趣的款，勾选代表加入本次推款清单，两套状态分别服务长期关注和当前客户。
The heart favorites styles the client likes; the check mark adds items to this pitch list. The two states serve different purposes.
详情页展示正面、背面、价格、借样费、尺码、库位和架杆，也推荐同品类近似款。
The detail page shows front and back images, price, loan fee, size, location, rack, and similar styles in the same category.
业务员多选后点击推款 PPT，系统自动生成客户可看的推款文件，并在我的中心留下记录。
After multi-selecting styles, sales clicks Pitch PPT. The system creates a client-ready presentation and stores the record in My Center.
客户想看实物时，业务员填写借用用途、预计归还时间和备注，提交借样申请到设计部后台。
When the client wants physical samples, sales fills purpose, return date, and notes, then submits a request to Design Admin.
样衣管理员在后台处理申请，按库位和架杆找样衣，确认借出；归还、丢失、损坏和淘汰都有记录。
The sample admin handles the request, finds items by location and rack, confirms the loan, and records returns, loss, damage, or retirement.
设计师上传正背面图，用 AI 生成白底图和补全字段，再填写价格、库位和架杆，新款入库后前台可见。
The designer uploads front and back images, uses AI for white-background images and field completion, then sets price, location, and rack.
问问云知可以回答趋势、报价、汇率和在库样衣问题，把 AI 放进业务员、设计师和样衣管理员的日常工作。
Ask Yunzhi answers trends, quotes, exchange rates, and inventory questions, putting AI into daily work for sales, designers, and admins.
管理层按业务组拉取周、月、年账单，分析客户和风格偏好，用数据提前准备下一季样衣。
Management pulls weekly, monthly, and yearly bills by team, analyzes client and style preferences, and prepares next-season samples from data.